## George.



# Software Engineer. Future Architect. Optimist.











## **MISSION STATEMENT**

I'm a deeply motivated London-based software engineer with 5 years of experience looking for high-impact, high-agency, high-velocity work where I can actually move the needle. My colleagues often note my ability to clearly communicate complex ideas, take a holistic view of problems and dig under the surface.

With a strong foundation, built under the mentorship of talented engineers at a Fortune 500 company, I'm ready for projects which allow me to keep learning at the fastest possible speed and apply the skills I have gained to moonshot projects which go against the grain.

## **EDUCATION**

## BSc Software Engineering (Digital and Technology Solutions)

Queen Mary University of London First Class

Bachelor of Science with Honours degree apprenticeship course composed of Computer Science Modules with additional workplace-directed project modules.

#### 4 A-Levels

**Exeter Mathematics School** 

A\*, A\*, A, A

Computer Science, Further Mathematics, Mathematics, Physics

## **OTHER PROJECTS**

## Pnyx: A foundation for decentralised democracy

Ongoing research effort into a fully decentralised, trustless and self-ratifying system for reaching consensus in a community.

Key Skills: Rust, LibP2P, Protobuf

### **Personal Site**

My personal space to explore UI/UX design. Also frontends my homelab infrastructure which includes password management, development tools and storage.

Key Skills: Vue, Nuxt, Tailwind, TypeScript

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Goldman Sachs International

Analyst - Counterparty Credit Risk Engineering

June 2024 - Present

Key Skills: Python, TypeScript, React, MongoDB, Podman

- » Spearheading a complete rearchitecture of the CCR data processing plant.
- » Established comprehensive tooling for build, deployment, execution, and monitoring of tasks, adding previously missing observability capabilities and improving developer experience.
- » Rewrote core daily batch processing steps, resulting in a 3x improvement in execution times and projected 80% reduction in overall plant processing time.
- » Onboarded new data processing improving analysis coverage.
- » Implemented cellular-granularity authorisation controls.
- » Delivered automated reporting functionality to senior leadership in line with regulatory requirements.
- » Designed and implemented new tool-based menu system in the UI to allow deeper user interaction and easier future expansion.

## Apprentice - Software Development and Lifecycle

May 2022 - June 2024

Key Skills: Kubernetes, GitLab, Linux, Java, Kaniko

- » Built monitoring tools enforcing quality and compliance controls across the internal GitLab instance.
- » Improved reliability and monitoring for the firm's custom internal deployment platform.
- » Upgraded developer tools for container builds.

## Apprentice - Prime Services Risk Analytics Engineering September 2020 - May 2022

Key Skills: Python, React, Java, SQL

- » Added full user preference functionality to two flagship applications.
- » Led evaluation efforts for new scheduling technologies.
- » Implemented the full processing pipeline for a new core risk management dataset.